name: 'can/can''t'
questions:
  -
    question: '$ watch TV after dinner?'
    answers:
      - 'do we can'
      - 'can we'
      - 'we can'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'I $ see the board.'
    answers:
      - 'don''t can'
      - 'do can''t'
      - 'can''t'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'James $ help us tomorrow.'
    answers:
      - can
      - 'can to'
      - 'does can'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: '$ come to class tomorrow?'
    answers:
      - 'can you'
      - 'you can'
      - 'do you can'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: '$ read my newspaper.'
    answers:
      - 'Can you'
      - 'You can'
      - 'You do can'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'We $ park here.'
    answers:
      - 'don''t can'
      - 'do can''t'
      - 'can''t'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ sit here?'
    answers:
      - 'Do I can'
      - 'Can I'
      - 'I can'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: '$ swim today?'
    answers:
      - 'Can we'
      - 'We can'
      - 'Do can we'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'Sorry, I $ remember your name.'
    answers:
      - 'don''t can'
      - 'can''t'
      - 'not can'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: '$ eat in a new restaurant.'
    answers:
      - 'We do can'
      - 'Can we'
      - 'We can'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ open the window?'
    answers:
      - 'Can I'
      - 'Do I can'
      - 'I can'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'She $ go to the movies tomorrow.'
    answers:
      - 'don''t can'
      - 'can''t'
      - 'not can'
    correct: 2
